evozi.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for evozi (www.evozi.com)**

**1\. Privacy Policy**

Evozi, Inc. (“Evozi”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to data collected by Evozi through www.evozi.com and the affiliate Facebook pages provided and owned by Evozi (collectively, the “Site”) and any other such service provided by Evozi (collectively, the “Service”). 

Evozi reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. Notice of material changes to either document will be posted on the Site’s homepage and/or will be provided by e-mailing you or notifying you upon login about these changes. However, Evozi encourages you to check this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service often for updates. 

This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Service. Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Terms of Service. Both the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service are legally binding on all users and you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. 

Please read all information as provided below. Evozi welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use or disclose personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). Any such questions or comments, or if more information regarding any item not listed below is needed, should be submitted via email to support[at]evozi[dot]com. 

At www.evozi.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.evozi.com and how it is used. 

**2\. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.evozi.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.evozi.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. We use "cookies" (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make evozi easier to use. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to evozi . We also use them to confirm that you are logged into evozi. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use evozi. 

**Google Cookies**  
• Google uses cookies to serve ads on www.evozi.com.  
• Google's use of the cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to www.evozi.com and other sites on the Internet.   
• Users may opt out of the use of the cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense  
AdBrite  

**www.evozi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.evozi.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**  

Evozi takes the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.

**3.** MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS. 

**3.1** Advertisements Displayed by Third Parties. Evozi may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Site. Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers’ sites. 

Date of last revision: Dec 14, 2011.
